bubblews.com 2015-10-29

# Privacy Policy - Bubblews

Bubblews.com, LLC respects your privacy. This privacy policy (this "Policy") informs you of our privacy practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used.

This Policy applies to all websites, servers and services owned or provided by Bubblews.com. Bubblews.com may add new sites, domain names or services from time to time. As explained below, this Policy applies only to websites owned and services maintained by Bubblews.com and not to websites or services to which links may be provided on Bubblews.com Sites.

BY USING THIS SITE, OR ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE OFFERED ON THIS SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY.

Bubblews.com Sites may provide links to independent websites for your convenience and information. If you access these links, you will leave our site. Bubblews.com does not control these independent sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from this Policy. Bubblews.com does not endorse or make any representations about any independent websites. The personal data you choose to provide to, or that is collected directly by, these independent sites is not covered by this Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of each and every website you visit on the Internet before submitting your personal information.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**2\. Collection of Personal Information**

Bubblews.com collects personal information from users of Bubblews.com Sites in connection with the access and use of the various products and services available to you on Bubblews.com Sites. These products and services may include: (i) registration for competitions and events; (ii) registration for receipt of communications like email updates and newsletters; (iii) registration for certain online community services and tools like message boards, chat rooms, forums, news groups or other community services; (iv) user surveys and polls; (v) participation in sweepstakes, contests or promotions by sponsored by Bubblews.com or third parties; and (vi) purchasing products and services.

**A.** Types of Information Collected. The types of personal information you provide to us may include your name, address, ZIP code, telephone number, email address, user IDs and passwords, age and date of birth, gender, product and service preferences and contact preferences.

**B.** Automatic Data Collection Tools. In addition to the information you provide us, Bubblews.com may also collect information during your visit to any Bubblews.com Site through the use of Automatic Data Collection Tools, which may include cookies, web beacons and other commonly used information-gathering tools. These tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website such as your browser type and language and access times. These tools may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address, clickstream behavior (i.e., the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take in connection with Bubblews.com Sites) and products and services you use. Bubblews.com may also use some of these Automatic Data Collection Tools in connection with certain emails sent from Bubblews.com and therefore may collect information using these tools when you open the email or click on a link contained in the email. Automatic Data Collection Tools are discussed further below.

**C.** Commingled Information. Bubblews.com may also collect information from commercially available sources that it deems credible. Such information may include your name, address, email address and demographic data. The information Bubblews.com collects from its commercial sources may be used along with the information Bubblews.com collects when you visit Bubblews.com Sites. For example, Bubblews.com may compare the geographic information acquired from commercial sources with the IP address collected by Automatic Data Collection Tools to derive your general geographic area.

**D.** Community Tools. From time to time, Bubblews.com may make message boards, chat rooms, forums, news groups and other community tools available to you on Bubblews.com Sites. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information in these public areas, your information becomes public information and can be viewed and used by Bubblews.com and others. We advise you to use caution in such public areas in disclosing personal information.

**3\. How We Use Your Personal Information**

We use the personal information you provide to us (i) in the manner described in this Policy, (ii) to improve and customize this site and the products and services offered to you, and (iii) as directed by you as indicated by your use of the products and services offered on this site. For example, we may use your personal information in connection with the following:

**A.** Creation of membership accounts;  
 **B.** Offers to participate in competitions and event;  
 **C.** Delivery of email updates and newsletters;  
 **D.** Communications of offers for promotions, sweepstakes and contests;  
 **E.** Invitations to participate in user surveys and polls;  
 **F.** Providing software updates and interactive materials.

We may also use your personal information to contact you offline concerning the products and services offered on this site.

**4\. Sharing of Personal Information**

Bubblews.com will not sell, rent or lease the personal information you provide. Bubblews.com will only share your personal information (i) with entities owned or controlled by Bubblews.com (ii) with your consent, (iii) with persons or entities engaged by Bubblews.com to carry out or fulfill Bubblews.com operations or business activities, and (iv) as otherwise stated in this Policy.

**A.** Entities Owned By Bubblews.com. We reserve the right to share your personal information with entities owned or controlled by Bubblews.com.

**B.** With Your Consent. We may offer services, competitions, events, contests, sweepstakes, promotions and other programs that are sponsored or co-sponsored with persons or entities not affiliated with Bubblews.com. When your consent is required for use of personal information that is not otherwise authorized by this Policy, we will seek to obtain your consent at the place where the information is collected either by an "opt-in" or "opt-out" method, or by other means (such as sending to you an e-mail). Based upon your voluntary participation in these programs, persons or entities other than Bubblews.com may obtain personal information that you submit as a condition of your participation. We cannot guarantee how these persons or entities will use your personal information.

**C.** Service Providers. Bubblews.com engages various suppliers and service providers to assist Bubblews.com in carrying out or fulfilling Bubblews.com operations and business activities. These suppliers and service providers may receive personal information you provide to us in connection with the performance of their obligations to Bubblews.com. If we do share personal information with suppliers and service providers, to the extent practical, we require that they protect such information in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. We cannot, however, guarantee how these entities will use your personal information.

**D.** Corporate Transactions. The personal information you provide is considered an asset of Bubblews.com and may transferred to a third party in connection with the merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets by Bubblews.com.

**E.** Legal Authorities. We reserve the right to access and disclose your personal information as necessary to (i) respond to any duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities, (ii) comply with any law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or order of any court or governmental authorities, and (iii) help prevent or investigate suspected fraud, harassment or violation of any law, rule, regulation, Bubblews.com policy or the terms and conditions of Bubblews.com Sites.

**5\. Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Information**

As described elsewhere in this Policy, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information (i.e., generic information that does not identify you personally) when you visit any Bubblews.com Site and otherwise. We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize the products and services offered on this site. We may also aggregate the information collected in a manner which does not identify any individual. We reserve the right to use this information in any manner we deem appropriate.

**6\. Collection of Information by Others**

Our site may contain links to independent websites not owned or operated by Bubblews.com. If you choose to access these links you will be leaving our site. These independent sites may be operated by our marketing, advertising and promotional partners, by suppliers and service providers to Bubblews.com, by our affiliates or otherwise. We do not endorse, screen or approve, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these independent websites. Some of these sites may have membership processes and privacy policies that are different from those of Bubblews.com. These sites may set their own cookies, collect data or solicit personal information. We have no control over the use of this information. We do not share the personal information you provide to us with these independent websites. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of each and every website you visit on the Internet.

**7\. Data Collection Tools**

Bubblews.com uses various automatic data collection tools in connection with Bubblews.com Sites. These tools may include the following, among others:

**A.** Cookies. Cookies are small data files transferred by a website to your computer's hard drive. Bubblews.com or its service providers may use cookies as a convenience feature to save you time, to understand how our site is used and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. Accepting the cookies used on our site or other sites where our ads appear may give us access to information about your browsing behavior, which we may use to personalize your experience on our site. We may also use cookies to offer you products, programs and services. Most browsers automatically accept cookies by default, but you can usually refuse cookies or selectively accept cookies by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If you turn off cookies, there may be some features of our site that will not be available to you and some Web pages may not display properly.

You can find information on popular browsers and how to adjust your cookie preferences at the following websites:

Microsoft Internet Explorer:  
<http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.ms>...

Mozilla Firefox:  
<http://www.mozilla.org/projects/security>...

**B.** Data Collection Tools of Third Parties. You should know that companies that advertise on Bubblews.com Sites and their agents and service providers may set their own cookies and web beacons when you click their advertising banners on Bubblews.com Sites. Information collected as a result of cookies and web beacons set by third party advertisers and their agents and service providers is subject to and controlled by the privacy practices of such third parties and Bubblews.com is not responsible for either the privacy practices of such third parties or the use of the information they collect.

**C.** Bubblews.com Advertisements on Third Party Websites. Bubblews.com or its service providers places ads on websites owned by third parties. These ads may send cookies from and use web beacons on these websites. The cookies and web beacons may enable Bubblews.com to collect information about the pages you view and the links on which you click from those pages and this information may be connected to the personal information you provide to us on Bubblews.com Sites.

**8\. Information Storage and Security**

The protection of your personal information is important to Bubblews.com. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure of this information, Bubblews.com utilizes appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures to safeguard the information we collect. However, no system can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard and we cannot guarantee that communications between you and us or the information stored on Bubblews.com Sites or our servers (or those of our agents and service providers) will be completely free from unauthorized access and disclosure and your use of any Bubblews.com Site demonstrates your assumption of this risk.

**9\. Changes to this Policy**

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to make changes to this Policy at any time and from time to time. Bubblews.com will undertake reasonable efforts to notify you of material changes to this Policy. We encourage you to review this Policy regularly for changes. Your continued use of Bubblews.com Sites following the posting of any changes to this Policy indicates your agreement to be bound by the terms of this Policy as revised.

If you have any other questions, comments or complaints about this Policy, please contact us email at support (at) bubblews (dot) com or write to us at:

Legal Counsel   
Bubblews.com, LLC   
4100 Monument Corner Drive   
Fairfax, Virginia 22030

**10\. Governing Law and Disputes**

This Policy is subject to the provisions set forth in the Terms of Service with respect to governing law and resolution of disputes.

**11\. International Users**

If you are visiting this site from a location outside the United States, your connection will be through servers located in the United States and all information you provide will be processed and maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using this site, you authorize the export of personal information to the United States and its storage and use as specified above. In addition, you acknowledge and agree to the provisions set forth above with respect to governing law and disputes.
